# Ashu Karande

Pune Maharashtra +91-8999361209 ashukarande05@gmail.com

## Programming Analyst

## **Summary**

A forward thinking developer offering **2 years and 6 months** of experience in building, integrating, testing and supporting web application. Experienced in working with clients, business managers and technical teams for executing concurrent projects.

#### Ready to work on new technologies.

Insightful knowledge of MVC, C#, SQL Server, SVN,VSS, JQuery, Javascript, ADO.Net,Amcharts. Working knowledge of Web API.

#### **Skills**

Programming and Scripting

Languages

ASP.Net MVC, C#, ADO.Net, JQuery, Javascript

**Database and Reporting** 

tool

SQL Server

**Code Control** 

SVN,VSS

Other

AmCharts, WEb API

## Awards and Recognition

#### **Distinguished Contributor Award**

Mar 2017 - Apr 2017

BNY Mellon India.

Received Distinguished contributor award for implementation of new layout and dashboards.

BOW Award

Sep 2017 - Oct 2017

BNY Mellon India.

BOW award for implementation of new layout, data analysis and dashboards.

## Work experience

#### Achemea Gross Report Automation / AIS Custody Reporting

Feb 2018 - Present

BNY Mellon India.

Applications to manage investment managers.

#### Achemea Gross Report Automation - Windows Application

- Used selenium for automation.
- Used excel reconciliation for reporting..

#### AIS Custody Reporting - Web Application.

- Used outlook for mail capture.
- Used R language for predictions.

• Designed UI and also developed scheduler.

#### Technologies Used: C#, ASP.Net MVC, SQL Server, JQuery, Selenium

#### Service Director Dashboards / Report Automation / PDF Prime Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

BNY Mellon India.

Applications to manage investment managers.

**Report Automation** - Windows Application.

• Used excel reconciliation for reporting.

Service Director Dashboard - Web Application.

- Developed for visualization purpose.
- This application will help organization keep transparency between clients and business, which will avoid the losses and manage the things easily.
- It will help keep watch on daily, monthly and yearly issues and supervisor activities.
- R language for data analysis.

**PDF Prime** - Windows Application

#### Technologies Used: C#, ASP.Net MVC, SQL Server, JQuery, Amcharts

#### Issue Tracker / Worpoint / PDF Prime Connect

March 2016 - Dec 2017

BNY Mellon India.

Applications to manage domestic as well as international audit.

Issue Tracker - Web Application.

Workpoint - Web Application.

**PDF Prime Connect** - Windows Application

Technologies Used: C#, ASP.Net MVC, SQL Server

#### **Education**

### **Bachelor of Computer Engineering**

2010 - 2014

Pune University

Completed Bachelor of Computer Engineering with 60.00 percentage.

**HSC** 2008 - 2010

Pune University

Completed HSC with 60.00 percentage.

#### **Personal Information**

Name: Ashu Karande.

Date of Birth: 05 Nov, 1992

Nationality: Indian Gender: Female

Languages Known: English, Hindi, Marathi

Marital Status: Single
Passport Valid: YES

Permanent Address: Chinchwad, Pune-019.

**Phone Number:** +91 8999361209 / +91 9146362907